<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<floater
 positioning="centered"
 legacy_header_height="18"
 height="440"
 layout="topleft"
 name="floater_about"
 help_topic="floater_about"
 save_rect="true"
 title="ABOUT [CAPITALIZED_APP_NAME]"
 width="470">
  <floater.string
     name="AboutHeader">
[APP_NAME] [VIEWER_VERSION_0].[VIEWER_VERSION_1].[VIEWER_VERSION_2] ([VIEWER_VERSION_3]) [BUILD_DATE] [BUILD_TIME] ([CHANNEL])
[[VIEWER_RELEASE_NOTES_URL] [ReleaseNotes]]

</floater.string>
  <floater.string
     name="AboutCompiler">
Built with [COMPILER] version [COMPILER_VERSION]

</floater.string>
  <floater.string
     name="AboutPosition">
You are at [POSITION_0,number,1], [POSITION_1,number,1], [POSITION_2,number,1] in [REGION] located at &lt;nolink&gt;[HOSTNAME]&lt;/nolink&gt; ([HOSTIP])
[SERVER_VERSION]
[SERVER_RELEASE_NOTES_URL]

</floater.string>
  <!-- *NOTE: Do not translate text like GPU, Graphics Card, etc -
       Most PC users who know what these mean will be used to the English versions,
       and this info sometimes gets sent to support. -->
  <floater.string
     name="AboutSystem">
CPU: [CPU]
Memory: [MEMORY_MB] MB
OS Version: [OS_VERSION]
Graphics Card Vendor: [GRAPHICS_CARD_VENDOR]
Graphics Card: [GRAPHICS_CARD]
</floater.string>
  <floater.string
     name="AboutDriver">
Windows Graphics Driver Version: [GRAPHICS_DRIVER_VERSION]
</floater.string>
  <floater.string
     name="AboutLibs">
OpenGL Version: [OPENGL_VERSION]

libcurl Version: [LIBCURL_VERSION]
J2C Decoder Version: [J2C_VERSION]
Audio Driver Version: [AUDIO_DRIVER_VERSION]
Qt Webkit Version: [QT_WEBKIT_VERSION]
Voice Server Version: [VOICE_VERSION]
</floater.string>
  <floater.string
     name="none">
      (none)
  </floater.string>
  <floater.string
     name="AboutTraffic">
Packets Lost: [PACKETS_LOST,number,0]/[PACKETS_IN,number,0] ([PACKETS_PCT,number,1]%)
</floater.string>
<floater.string
     name="ErrorFetchingServerReleaseNotesURL">
Error fetching server release notes URL.
</floater.string>
  <tab_container
    follows="all" 
    top="25"
    left="10"
    height="405" 
    width="450" 
    name="about_tab"
    tab_position="top">
    <panel
      border="true" 
      label="Info"
      help_topic="about_support_tab"
      name="support_panel">
      <text_editor
        parse_urls="true" 
       follows="top|left"
       font="SansSerif"
       height="343"
       bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
       left="5"
       max_length="65536"
       name="support_editor"
       top="5"
       width="435"
       word_wrap="true" />
      <button
        follows="left|top" 
        label="Copy to Clipboard"
        name="copy_btn"
        left="10"
        top_pad="5"
        height="25"
        width="180" />
    </panel>
    <panel
      border="true" 
      label="Credits" 
      help_topic="about_credits_tab"
      name="credits_panel">
      <text
          follows="top|left|right"
          height="10"
          layout="topleft"
          left="5"
          name="linden_intro"
          top="10"
          width="435"
          wrap="true">
Second Life is brought to you by the Lindens:
      </text>
      <text_editor
       enabled="false" 
       follows="top|left"
       height="98"
       bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
       left="5"
       text_color="LtGray"
       max_length="65536"
       name="linden_names"
       top_pad="10"
       width="435"
       word_wrap="true">
Philip, Andrew, Doug, Richard, Phoenix, Ian, Mark, Robin, Dan, Char, Ryan, Eric, Jim, Lee, Jeff, Michael, Kelly, Steve, Catherine, Bub, Ramzi, Jill, Jeska, Don, Kona, Callum, Charity, Jack, Shawn, babbage, James, Lauren, Blue, Brent, Reuben, Pathfinder, Jesse, Patsy, Torley, Bo, Cyn, Jonathan, Gia, Annette, Ginsu, Harry, Lex, Runitai, Guy, Cornelius, Beth, Swiss, Thumper, Wendy, Teeple, Seth, Dee, Mia, Sally, Liana, Aura, Beez, Milo, Red, Gulliver, Marius, Joe, Jose, Dore, Justin, Nora, Morpheus, Lexie, Amber, Chris, Xan, Leyla, Walker, Sabin, Joshua, Hiromi, Tofu, Fritz, June, Jean, Ivy, Dez, Ken, Betsy, Which, Spike, Rob, Zee, Dustin, George, Claudia, del, Matthew, jane, jay, Adrian, Yool, Rika, Yoz, siobhan, Qarl, Benjamin, Beast, Everett, madhavi, Christopher, Izzy, stephany, Jeremy, sean, adreanne, Pramod, Tobin, sejong, Iridium, maurice, kj, Meta, kari, JP, bert, kyle, Jon, Socrates, Bridie, Ivan, maria, Aric, Coco, Periapse, sandy, Storrs, Lotte, Colossus, Brad, Pastrami, Zen, BigPapi, Banzai, Sardonyx, Mani, Garry, Jaime, Neuro, Samuel, Niko, CeeLo, Austin, Soft, Poppy, emma, tessa, angelo, kurz, alexa, Sue, CG, Blake, Erica, Brett, Bevis, kristen, Q, simon, Enus, MJ, laurap, Kip, Scouse, Ron, Ram, kend, Marty, Prospero, melissa, kraft, Nat, Seraph, Hamilton, Lordan, Green, miz, Ashlei, Trinity, Ekim, Echo, Charlie, Rowan, Rome, Jt, Doris, benoc, Christy, Bao, Kate, Tj, Patch, Cheah, Johan, Brandy, Angela, Oreh, Cogsworth, Lan, Mitchell, Space, Bambers, Einstein, Bender, Malbers, Matias, Maggie, Rothman, Milton, Niall, Marin, Allison, Mango, Andrea, Katt, Yi, Ambroff, Rico, Raymond, Gail, Christa, William, Dawn, Usi, Dynamike, M, Corr, Dante, Molly, kaylee, Danica, Kelv, Lil, jacob, Nya, Rodney, elsie, Blondin, Grant, Nyx, Devin, Monty, Minerva, Keira, Katie, Jenn, Makai, Clare, Joy, Cody, Gayathri, FJ, spider, Oskar, Landon, Jarv, Noelle, Al, Doc, Gray, Vir, t, Maestro, Simone, Shannon, yang, Courtney, Scott, charlene, Quixote, Susan, Zed, Amanda, Katelin, Esbee, JoRoan, Enkidu, roxie, Scarlet, Merov, Kevin, Judy, Rand, Newell, Les, Dessie, Galen, Michon, Geo, Siz, Calyle, Pete, Praveen, Callen, Sheldon, Pink, Nelson, jenelle, Terrence, Nathan, Juan, Sascha, Huseby, Karina, Kaye, Kotler, Lis, Darv, Charrell, Dakota, Kimmora, Theeba, Taka, Mae, Perry, Ducot, dana, Esther, Dough, gisele, Doten, Viale, Fisher, jessieann, ashley, Torres, delby, rountree, kurt, Slaton, Madison, Rue, Gino, Wen, Casssandra, Brodesky, Squid, Gez, Rakesh, Gecko, Ladan, Tony, Tatem, Squire, Falcon, BK, Crimp, Tiggs, Bacon, Coyot, Carmilla, Webb, Sea, Arch, Jillian, Jason, Bernard, Vogt, Peggy, dragon, Pup, xandix, Wallace, Bewest, Inoshiro, Rhett, AG, Aimee, Ghengis, Itiaes, Eli, Steffan, Epic, Grapes, Stone, Prep, Scobu, Robert, Alain, Carla, Vicky, Tia, Alec, Taras, Lisa, Oz, Ariane, Log, House, Kazu, Kim, Drofnas, Tyler, Campbell, Michele, Madeline, Nelly, Baron, Thor, Lori, Hele, Fredrik, Teddy, Pixie, Berry, Gabrielle, Alfonso, Brooke, Wolf, Ringo, Cru, Charlar, Rodvik, Gibson, Elise, Bagman, Greger, Leonidas, Jerm, Leslie, CB, Brenda, Durian, Carlo, mm, Zeeshan, Caleb, Max, Elikak, Mercille, Steph, Chase
      </text_editor>
      <text
          follows="top|left"
          height="10"
          layout="topleft"
          left="5"
          name="contrib_intro"
          top_pad="10"
          width="435"
          wrap="true">
with open source contributions from:
      </text>
      <text_editor
       enabled="false" 
       follows="top|left"
       height="98"
       bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
       left="5"
       text_color="LtGray"
       max_length="65536"
       name="contrib_names"
       top_pad="10"
       width="435"
       word_wrap="true">
Dummy Name replaced at run time
      </text_editor>
      <text
          follows="top|left"
          height="10"
          layout="topleft"
          left="5"
          name="trans_intro"
          top_pad="10"
          width="435"
          wrap="true">
and translations from:
      </text>
      <text_editor
       enabled="false" 
       follows="top|left"
       height="98"
       bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
       left="5"
       text_color="LtGray"
       max_length="65536"
       name="trans_names"
       top_pad="10"
       width="435"
       word_wrap="true">
Dummy Name replaced at run time
      </text_editor>
    </panel>
    <panel
      border="true"
      label="Licenses"
      help_topic="about_licenses_tab"
      name="licenses_panel">
      <text_editor
       enabled="false"
       follows="left|top"
       height="375"
       bg_readonly_color="Transparent"
       left="5"
       text_color="LtGray"
       max_length="65536"
       name="credits_editor"
       top="5"
       width="435"
       word_wrap="true">
        3Dconnexion SDK Copyright (C) 1992-2009 3Dconnexion
        APR Copyright (C) 2011 The Apache Software Foundation
        Collada DOM Copyright 2006 Sony Computer Entertainment Inc.
        cURL Copyright (C) 1996-2010, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
        DBus/dbus-glib Copyright (C) 2002, 2003  CodeFactory AB / Copyright (C) 2003, 2004 Red Hat, Inc.
        expat Copyright (C) 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
        FreeType Copyright (C) 1996-2002, 2006 David Turner, Robert Wilhelm, and Werner Lemberg.
        GL Copyright (C) 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
        GLOD Copyright (C) 2003-04 Jonathan Cohen, Nat Duca, Chris Niski, Johns Hopkins University and David Luebke, Brenden Schubert, University of Virginia.
        google-perftools Copyright (c) 2005, Google Inc.
        Havok.com(TM) Copyright (C) 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
        jpeg2000 Copyright (C) 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
        jpeglib Copyright (C) 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
        ogg/vorbis Copyright (C) 2002, Xiphophorus
        OpenSSL Copyright (C) 1998-2008 The OpenSSL Project.
        PCRE Copyright (c) 1997-2012 University of Cambridge
        SDL Copyright (C) 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
        SSLeay Copyright (C) 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
        xmlrpc-epi Copyright (C) 2000 Epinions, Inc.
        zlib Copyright (C) 1995-2012 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.

        Second Life Viewer uses Havok (TM) Physics. (c)Copyright 1999-2010 Havok.com Inc. (and its Licensors). All Rights Reserved. See www.havok.com for details.

        This software contains source code provided by NVIDIA Corporation.

        All rights reserved.  See licenses.txt for details.

        Voice chat Audio coding: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)
      </text_editor>
      </panel>
    </tab_container>
</floater>
