<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<teleport_messages>
	<message_set name="errors">
		<message name="invalid_tport">
			Problem encountered processing your teleport request. You may need to log back in before you can teleport.
如果你持續得到此訊息，請查閱 [SUPPORT_SITE]。
		</message>
		<message name="invalid_region_handoff">
			Problem encountered processing your region crossing. You may need to log back in before you can cross regions.
如果你持續得到此訊息，請查閱 [SUPPORT_SITE]。
		</message>
		<message name="blocked_tport">
			抱歉，目前瞬間傳送已被阻擋。請稍後再試。
如果你仍無法進行瞬間傳送，請登出後重新入來解決此一問題。
		</message>
		<message name="nolandmark_tport">
			抱歉，不過系統無法找到地標所在目的地。
		</message>
		<message name="timeout_tport">
			抱歉，不過系統無法完成瞬間傳送的聯接。
請稍後再試。
		</message>
		<message name="NoHelpIslandTP">
		您不能瞬间转移回“援助岛”。
去“公共援助岛”重复您的教程。
		</message>
		<message name="noaccess_tport">
			抱歉，你並沒有權限進入要瞬間傳送的目的地。
		</message>
		<message name="missing_attach_tport">
			Your attachments have not arrived yet. Try waiting for a few more seconds or log out and back in again before attempting to teleport.
		</message>
		<message name="too_many_uploads_tport">
			The asset queue in this region is currently clogged so your teleport request will not be able to succeed in a timely manner. Please try again in a few minutes or go to a less busy area.
		</message>
		<message name="expired_tport">
			Sorry, but the system was unable to complete your teleport request in a timely fashion. Please try again in a few minutes.
		</message>
		<message name="expired_region_handoff">
			Sorry, but the system was unable to complete your region crossing in a timely fashion. Please try again in a few minutes.
		</message>
		<message name="no_host">
			Unable to find teleport destination. The destination may be temporarily unavailable or no longer exists. Please try again in a few minutes.
		</message>
		<message name="no_inventory_host">
			收納區功能目前無法使用。
		</message>
	</message_set>
	<message_set name="progress">
		<message name="sending_dest">
			Sending to destination.
		</message>
		<message name="redirecting">
			重新導向至不同位置。
		</message>
		<message name="relaying">
			Relaying to destination.
		</message>
		<message name="sending_home">
			送出家位置的要求。
		</message>
		<message name="sending_landmark">
			地標位置要求瞬間傳送中。
		</message>
		<message name="completing">
			瞬間傳送完成。
		</message>
		<message name="completed_from">
			由 [T_SLURL] 瞬間傳送完成。
		</message>
		<message name="resolving">
			目的地解決中。
		</message>
		<message name="contacting">
			聯繫到新的地區。
		</message>
		<message name="arriving">
			抵達中...
		</message>
		<message name="requesting">
			瞬間傳送要求中...
		</message>
	</message_set>
</teleport_messages>
